<resources>
    <string-array name="probes">
        <item>Notice your breath - wherever you can sense it most easily.</item>
        <item>Follow your breath while focusing on a place where you can feel it the least.</item>
        <item>You don\'t need to locate your breath in a specific location. Just be aware of it - however it appears.</item>
        <item>Notice the sensations of the breath in the belly.</item>
        <item>Notice the sensations of the breath in the chest.</item>
        <item>Notice the sensations of the breath at the nostrils.</item>
        <item>Notice the breath as a whole.</item>
        <item>Notice how the whole body is breathing.</item>
        <item>Notice how, in a way, the breath is everywhere.</item>
        <item>Notice how the breath is a continuous flow of sensations.</item>
        <item>When noticing your breath, zoom further in to note the sensations that make up those sensations.</item>
        <item>You may discover more and more sensations that belong to the breath.</item>
        <item>Notice if there are parts of your breath you are pulling away from.</item>
        <item>Notice if there are parts of your breath you are pushing away.</item>
        <item>Notice if there are parts of your breath you are pulled towards.</item>
        <item>Notice if there are parts of your breath you are pushing towards.</item>
        <item>Notice if you are rather approaching your breath, moving away from it, or neither.</item>
        <item>Note what can be sensed between out-breath and in-breath.</item>
        <item>Note what can be sensed between in-breath and out-breath.</item>
        <item>You may try to lean a tiny bit forward.</item>
        <item>You may try to lean a tiny bit backwards.</item>
        <item>You may try to open your jaw a tiny bit further.</item>
        <item>You may try to close your jaw a tiny bit more.</item>
        <item>What if you don\'t care about the sensations of your breath at all?</item>
        <item>This time, don\'t focus at all.</item>
        <item>Notice that your body is constantly moving (you\'re not a Stone Buddha).</item>
        <item>Notice how there are movements everywhere in the body.</item>
        <item>Notice how sensations arise in awareness without you doing anything.</item>
        <item>What if you watched each breath as something precious?</item>
        <item>What if you watched each breath as if it was the most unremarkable thing?</item>
        <item>What if you watched your breath with "disinterested interest"?</item>
        <item>There may be thoughts that catch you quicker than you even notice.</item>
        <item>There may be thoughts that seem more intriguing than the breath.</item>
        <item>What if the breath belonged to someone you care for?</item>
        <item>Observe the breath through the eyes of someone who cares for you.</item>
        <item>What is there between the thoughts?</item>
        <item>What is there beyond your current sensory experience?</item>
        <item>Try to zoom in and zoom out simultaneously.</item>
        <item>In a way, the breath is watching you.</item>
        <item>If there are thoughts, restrict them to current moment.</item>
        <item>Can you follow the mind wherever it moves?</item>
        <item>Pick an experiment that you enjoyed before.</item>
        <item>Pick an experience (however small) from the current session that surprised you (i.e., that you didn\'t see coming) and focus on that.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
